6달러요
Six dollars, please.
6달러?
하루 지났으니까 3달러죠
Six? I just had it for one night.
It's three.
8시가 마감인데
지금 8시 2분이에요
Eight o'clock's the cutoff.
And, oh, it's 8:02.
정말 엿장수 맘대로
하시는 군요
You know, in a weird way,
you have too much power.
You have to help me
because I only have three.
3달러 밖에 없으니까
이걸로 해결하세요
내가 도와줄게
I can help with that.
Oh, my God. Richard?
하느님!
리차드?
- 안녕하세요?
- 안녕!
얼굴이 까칠해 보이네요
Your lip went bald.
고마워요
Thanks.
넌 여전하다
You look great!
Right.
그래요?
No, you do. You....
정말이야, 넌...
What?
네?
You got panties stuck to your leg.
팬티가 다리에 붙어있어
I was just grabbing some things
out of the dryer, and static cling.
빨래 건조기 정전기 때문에
종종 이래요
Or maybe God knew I'd be running into
you and saw an opportunity.
아니면 하느님께서 우리가
재밌게 만나라고 붙였겠죠
It's good to see you.
만나서 반가워
저도 기뻐요
It's good to see you too.
The One Where
Monica and Rich are Just Friends
성인영화
See that guy?
He's in "Classics" now...
저 남자 보이죠?
고전명화 코너에 있다가
... but as soon as we leave,
he's going straight to the porn.
우리가 나가자마자
야한 영화를 고를 거예요
'시민 케인'과 '현기증' 사이에
'젖소부인'을 끼워서 빌릴 거야
He'll go to the counter with Citizen
Kane, Vertigo and Clockwork Orgy.
This is nice.
정말 좋군
- 네
- 만나고 싶었어
-I miss this.
-Me too.
저두요
햄버거라도 먹으러 갈까?
You want to get a hamburger
or something?
그래도 될지 모르겠어요
I don't know if that's a good idea.
Just friends.
I won't grope you. I promise.
우리는 친구잖아
잡아먹지 않을게
I think it's too soon.
아뇨,
너무 빠른 거 같아서요
빠르지 않아
점심을 일찍 먹었거든
No, it's not too soon.
I had lunch at 11.
신난다!
Yeah, baby!
-What are you making?
-Chocolate milk. Want some?
뭐해?
쵸코렛 우유 만드는데
마실래?
됐어, 난 29살이야
No, thanks. I'm 29.
Oh, my God! I gotta go to work!
세상에, 나 늦겠어
오늘은 몇 시에 퇴근해?
What time will you get off tonight?
모르겠어
많이 늦을 거 같아
It could be really late.
이런, 또야?
Not again!
미안해
그럼 약속을 정하자
I know. I'm sorry.
I'll make a deal with you, okay?
Every night that you're asleep
before I get home...
내가 귀가하기 전에
자기가 잠이 들면...
... I will wake you up in a way
that has proved popular in the past.
자기가 좋아하는 방식으로
깨워줄게
Well, if you need to stay late,
I want to be supportive of that.
자기가 늦게까지 일해야하면
나도 신체 리듬을 바꿔야지
- 안녕
- 왔니
Look at you.
Since when do you rollerblade?
언제부터 그걸 탔어?
Since tomorrow.
내일부터
I met a cute guy in the park.
공원에서 이상형을 만났어
And he jogs and blades and swims
and so we made a deal.
만능 운동선수더라구
약속을 정했어
He's gonna teach me how
to do jock stuff.
그 사람한테 운동 배울 거야
-And what are you gonna do for him?
-I'm gonna let him.
그 남자가 바라는 건 뭔데?
- 내가 배우는 거
- 좋겠다
Cool.
Good morning.
잘 잤어?
- 안녕
Somebody got in late last night.
어젯밤에 늦게 들어왔더라
리차드를 만났어
Yeah, well, I ran into Richard.
- 뭐?
- 언제 그렇게 됐어?
When did this happen?
8시 2분에
Around 8:02.
잠시 대화를 나누다가
조용히 햄버거만 먹었어
We talked for a while, and then
we went out for an innocent burger.
그럼 햄버거가 떠들었겠네
There's no such thing as
an "innocent burger."
-Gonna see him again?
-Tomorrow night.
- 또 만날 거야?
- 내일 밤에
Monica, what are you doing?
정말 그러고 싶어?
She spent six months
getting over him...
6개월 간 잊고 싶었던 남자를
다시 만나 데이트를 한다잖아
...and now she's celebrating that
by going on a date with him.
It's not a date, okay?
데이트 아냐
I'm teaching him how to make a
lasagna for a potluck dinner.
저녁에 간단하게 먹을 수 있는
라자냐 요리법을 알려줄 거야
될 수 있으면 많이 만들어
같이 자고 나면 배고파질 테니까
You might want to make extra, because
you'll be hungry after the sex.
We're not gonna have sex.
같이 잘 일은 없어
변한 것도 없구
Nothing's changed here. He still
doesn't want children, and I still do.
여전히 그이는 애를
원치 않고, 난 원해
So we're just gonna be friends.
그러니까 그냥 친구인 거야
말처럼 쉬우면!
Naked friends.
- 안녕
-Do you have any ice?
-Check the freezer.
얼음 있니?
냉장고에 봐
거기 없으면 다 먹은 거야
If there's none in there,
we're probably out.
Are you just getting home?
It's late.
지금 퇴근했어?
너무 늦다
I know.
I had the greatest day, though.
알아, 그래도 기분은 좋아
캘빈 클라인 부서장들하고
회의가 있었는데
I went to a meeting
with reps from Calvin Klein.
I liked a line of lingerie, so my boss
ordered a ton of it. And you?
란제리 선이 예쁘다고 했더니
우리 사장이 주문을 많이 했어
넌 뭐했어?
I discovered I'm able to count all my
teeth using just my tongue.
혀를 이용해서
내 이빨 숫자를 세 봤어
Why do you have a copy of
The Shining in your freezer?
왜 냉장고 안에
'샤이닝' 책이 있어?
어제 그거 읽다가
너무 무서워서...
I was reading it last night
and I got scared, so....
냉장고에 넣으면 안심이 돼?
But you're safe from it
if it's in the freezer?
Well, safer.
당연하지
I never start reading it...
난 냉장고에 빈자리가 있어야
'샤이닝'을 손에 들어
...without making sure
we got room in the freezer.
How often do you read it?
자주 읽나보지?
같은 책 여러 번
본 적 있어?
Haven't you ever read a book
over and over again?
'작은 아씨들'은 여러 번 봤어
그 책은 고전이잖아
I read Little Women more than once.
It's a classic.
What's so great about The Shining?
'샤이닝'은 뭐가 좋아?
The question should be, what is
not so great about The Shining?
질문을 바꿔서
'샤이닝'의 뭐가 싫으냐고 물어줘
내 답은 "전혀 없다"야
And the answer would be,
"nothing." All right?
공포소설로는 최고지
네가 말한 '고전' 이상이야
This is the scariest book ever.
I bet it's better than that
classic of yours.
그래?
We'll just see about that, okay?
과연 그럴까?
I will read The Shining,
and you will read Little Women.
난 '샤이닝'을 읽어볼게
넌 '작은 아씨들'을 읽어
- 좋아, 해보자
- 정말이지?
All right, you got it.
- 그래
- 좋아
Now, Rach, these little women....
- '작은 아씨들'이라고 했지?
- 응
How little are they?
얼마나 작은데?
I mean, are they, like, scary little?
겁나게 작니?
챈들러, 로스?
여긴 로버트야
Chandler, Ross? This is Robert.
- 반가워요
- 저두요
You have lipstick right here.
립스틱이 묻었어
That's okay, it's mine.
We just kissed.
내 거니까 괜찮아
방금 키스했거든
Isn't it a bit cold out for shorts?
그런 반바지 춥지 않아요?
전 캘리포니아 출신이에요
Well, I'm from California.
Right. Sometimes you guys
just burst into flame.
그렇군요
그래서 열이 많군요?
나 일어난다, 일어났어
뭐 마실 사람?
I'm up. I'm up. I've gotten up now.
Anybody want anything?
-I'll have coffee.
-Me too.
- 난 커피 줘
- 저두요
나까지 셋!
Make that three.
알았어
로스, 나 좀 보자
Ross, why don't you come with me?
그래
어디 불편해? 왜 그래?
What's the matter?
What's going on?
Robert's coming out.
로버트 속보여
What do you mean?
Is he gay?
뭐?
늑대 같은 놈이라구?
아니...
He's coming out of his shorts.
반바지 속이 보인다구
뭐?
What?
거시기가 다 보여
The man is showing brain.
Are you sure? Hold on.
정말이야?
잠깐만
I'm sorry.
That was a coffee and a....
미안한데... 커피랑...
- 커피요
- 알았어요
Coffee. We could write it down.
- 주문서 적어줘요?
- 아뇨, 됐어요
No, no. That won't be necessary.
그럴... 필요는 없죠
Well?
- 봤어?
- 그래, 그래
What do we do? What do we do?
이제 어쩌지?
정면 응시만 피하면 돼
Well, I suppose we just
try to not look directly at it.
Like an eclipse.
보여도 없는 척!
사람들이 내 요리
칭찬하면 뭐라고 하지?
When people compliment my
cooking tonight, what do I say?
'고마워요'라고 답하고
저한테 예쁜 거 사주세요
You say, "Thank you."
Then you buy me something pretty.
오세요, 여기에 손을 넣고
토마토를 으깨야돼요
Come on, we're gonna
put our hands in this bowl...
...and we're gonna start
squishing the tomatoes.
This feels very weird.
느낌이 이상하네
You touch people's eyeballs
and this feels weird?
사람들 눈만 보시는 분이
이게 뭐가 이상해요?
눈만 만지지
으깨본 적은 없거든
Sure, I touch them. But I spent years
learning not to squish them.
That's my hand.
그거 내 손이야
-Keep squishing.
-The tomatoes are squishing.
좋아
- 계속 하세요
- 토마토를 으깨자!
You got some on your shirt.
저런, 셔츠에 튀었어요
- 응
- 잠깐만요
Hold on a second.
소다수로 닦아내면...
바로 지워져요
Just put a little club soda on it.
Get to it right away.
이러면...
It should do...
...the trick.
간단하죠
What?
왜?
바지에도 묻었어요
You've got some on your pants.
I'll just throw them out.
그냥 버리면 돼
These little women!
이게 '작은 아씨들'이야?
You're liking it?
- 맘에 들어?
- 응
Oh, yeah.
Amy just burned Jo's manuscript.
에이미가 '조'의 원고를 태워
녀석이 어떻게 용서를 했을까?
I don't see how he could forgive her.
Jo's a girl.
It's short for Josephine.
'조'는 여자야
조세핀의 애칭이지
But Jo's got a crush on Laurie.
'조'가 로리에게 반하던데
You mean it's like a girl-girl thing?
그럼 이거 레즈비언 얘기야?
That is the one thing missing
from The Shining.
사실 '샤이닝'에는
그런 게 아쉬웠어
No, actually, Laurie's a boy.
로리는 남자야
No wonder Rachel had to read this so
many times.
이렇게 복잡하니
여러 번 읽는구나
- 우리 왔어
- 안녕
농구 강습은 잘돼?
How'd the basketball go?
레이업슛, 프리 드로우
23점 슛도 배웠어
I learned how to shoot a lay-up,
a foul shot, and a 23-pointer.
You mean a 3-pointer?
3점 슛이겠지?
난 23점이래, 우아해서
I get more because I'm dainty.
여기 공중전화는 어딨어?
Is there a phone here
to check my messages?
뒤에 있어, 동전 줄까?
-ln back. Do you want a quarter?
-I always carry one in my sock.
됐어, 양말 속에 갖고 다녀
What are you doing?
Get back on your side
너 왜 그래?
저쪽으로 가...
안녕하쇼?
Hello!
- 조이에요, 반가워요
- 저두요, 로버트입니다
I'm Joey. We haven't met.
Good to meet you. Robert.
What?
뭐야?
What? You guys, what is going on?
왜들 그래?
로버트가 싫어?
Do you not like Robert?
왜 웃는 거야?
Why are you laughing?
묻지마, 너도 곧 보게 돼
Calm down.
No reason to get testy.
-You guys! Come on!
-We're sorry.
제발 그만 좀 해
미안해, 정말
로버트가 너무 솔직해서...
It just seems that Robert isn't as
concealed in the shorts area...
특히 반바지 쪽이...
일부러 인지 몰라도
...as one may have hoped.
무슨 소리야?
What do you mean?
- 왔어
- 응
로버트? 있잖아요...
Could you pass me those cookies?
- 거기 과자 좀 줄래요?
- 그러죠
Sure.
So how'd the lasagna go over?
사람들 반응은 어땠어요?
정말? 잘 됐네요
그럼 선물 3개 사줘요
Really? Good. So you owe me three
pretty things.
저도 당신 생각 많이 해요
I've been thinking about you too.
아뇨
우린 플라토닉에 가까워요
Well, no. It's hard,
this "platonomy" thing.
플라스틱 말구요!
It's a word.
저는 이런 상태가 좋아요
우린 잘하고 있어요
I do think it's better this way.
We're being smart.
Yes, I'm sure.
네, 확신해요
You really sure?
정말 확신해?
I'll call you back.
다음에 통화해요
그럼 우린 함께 잠을
잘 수 있는 친구죠?
So we can be friends
who sleep together.
그렇지
함께 하는 활동 중 하나지
Absolutely.
This'll just be something we do.
라켓볼 같은 거
Like racquetball.
Sounds smart and healthy to me.
그것도 같이 하면 좋겠죠
So just out of curiosity...
그냥 물어보는 건데요...
함께 라켓볼 치는
사람이 있나요?
...do you currently have
any other "racquetball" buddies?
Just your dad.
네 아버지
Although that's actually racquetball.
물론 우린 라켓볼만 치지
다음 화요일에 여자를
소개받기로 했어
You know, I do have a blind date...
...with my sister's neighbor
next Tuesday.
Do you want me to cancel it?
취소할까?
아뇨
No!
안 되요
나 때문에 그런 약속을
취소하는 건 싫어요
Because if you did,
that means you'd be canceling for me.
우린 친구잖아요
-And we're just friends.
-Exactly.
그렇지
안녕!
Oh, don't sit down.
앉지마
-Ready to go?
-You bet.
- 타격 연습하러 가야지
- 응, 좋아
여기, 선물 받아
And first, here's a gift.
이런!
Stretchy pants?!
고탄력 바지?
세상에서 제일 좋은
선물이지
The greatest things in the world!
If I were you, I'd wear them every day.
내가 당신이라면
매일 매일 입을 걸요
고마워, 정말...
정말 좋다
Gee, thank you.
Really, that's so nice.
그런데 솔직히 말하면
난 이런 거 못 입어
But, to be honest,
I don't think I can wear these.
너무 끼면,
몸이 드러나잖아
They're so tight.
I'd feel like I'm on display.
I'm sorry.
미안해
괜찮아, 난 그저...
That's all right. I'll figure....
- 안녕하세요?
- 네
How's it going?
- 나 왔다
- 그래
Good.
'샤이닝' 어디까지 읽었어?
How's The Shining?
Danny just went into Room 217.
대니가 방에 들어섰다
217페이지
The next part's the best!
That dead lady in the bathtub
다음 장면이 죽이지
욕조의 시체가...
안돼, 안돼!
미리 알면 재미없어
You're gonna ruin it!
알았어, 암호로 할게
I'll talk in code.
Remember when the kid sees
those two "blanks" in the hallway?
꼬마가 복도에서 그걸 보잖아
Yeah, that's very cool.
그래, 섬뜩하지
모든 그게, 그거하고,
그렇잖아
All "blank" and no "blank" makes
"blank" a "blank-blank."
No, the end!
아냐, 아냐, 마지막에
잭이 그걸로 거의 다
죽일 뻔했는데, 도망가지?
Jack almost kills them
with the "blank"...
... but in the last second,
they get away.
조이, 말하지 말랬잖아!
I can't believe you just did that.
암호 해독도 잘하네!
I can't believe she cracked your code.
그렇다면, 좋아
Okay. Laurie proposes to Jo
and she says no...
로리의 청혼을 '조'가 거절해
사랑하는 데도 말야
...even though she's in love with him.
Then he ends up marrying Amy.
로리는 에이미와 결혼해
난 우연히 튀어나온 말이었어!
Mine was by accident!
보일러가 터져서
호텔이 무너지고 아버지도 죽어
The boiler explodes and destroys the
hotel and kills the dad.
Beth dies.
베스가 죽어
베스...
베스가 죽어?
Beth dies?
Is that true?
If I keep reading, is Beth gonna die?
정말이야?
착한 베스가 죽는 단 말야?
No, Beth doesn't die.
She doesn't die. Does she, Rachel?
아냐, 안 죽어
베스 안 죽지, 레이첼?
뭐?
조이는, 잭 니콜슨이 주연을
맡지 않은 영화의 원작을
He's asking if you've ruined...
...the first book he's ever loved
that didn't star Jack Nicholson.
열심히 읽었는데
헛수고했냐는 뜻이야
No. She doesn't die.
그래, 안 죽어
그럼 왜 그런 말을 해?
Then why would you say that?
왜냐면...
Because I wanted to hurt you.
네가 너무 얄미워서
여기 있군
열쇠를 떨어뜨려서요
Oh, there they are.
I dropped my keys.
세상에!
Got them.
찾았어요
나 왔어!
Sorry. I'm sorry.
미안해
오늘 정말 끔찍했어
한꺼번에 일이 밀렸어
You would not believe my day.
I had to work two shifts.
And then to top it off...
요리가 끝나갈 쯤에
내 가슴 패드를 잃어버렸어
... I lost one of my fake boobs
in a grill fire.
불에 탔어
What are you smiling at?
왜 웃는 거야?
많이 놀랬겠다고 생각했어
I was thinking your day
could still pick up.
응, 맞아
안녕!
I love this "friend" thing!
친구가 좋긴 좋군요
로버트가 금방 올거야
Robert's gonna be here any second,
so could one of you just tell him?
누가 좀 말해줄래?
Please, right now.
제발 부탁이야
그 사람 볼 때마다
자꾸 상상이 돼서 미치겠어
Every time I see him, it's "ls it
on the loose? Is it watching me?"
우린 말못해
We can't tell him.
친하지도 않은 남자한테
어떻게 해?
You can't go up to a guy you barely
know and talk about his "stuff."
그거 보인다고!
맞아, 보기 좋다고
칭찬할 수도 없고
He's right. Even if it's
to say something complimentary.
- 안녕
- 왔어?
You ready for the gym?
체육관으로 가자
There's a new rock-climbing
wall. We can spot each other.
암벽 등반 시설을 해놨대
서로 약점을 보완할 수 있어
Yeah, I can spot you from here.
여기서도 할 수 있어
What?
뭐?
잘 들어, 로버트...
Listen, Robert....
Hey, don't we have to...?
- 꼭 그걸 말해야...
- 응, 그럴 필요...
Yeah, we got....
넌 참 괜찮은 남자야
I think you're really, really great.
이런! 언제나 똑같군
Oh, God. Here we go again.
왜 맨날 이러는 거지?
너무 솔직한 게 탈인가?
Why does this keep happening?
Is it something I'm putting out there?
내 잘못이야?
아님 내가 멍청인가?
Is this my fault? Or am I just nuts?
나도 뭐라 해야할지
모르겠어
I don't know what to say.
Hey, buddy? This is a family place.
Put the mouse back in the house.
젊은 친구!
여긴 공공장소야
고추는 고추밭에
있어야지
정말 볼래요?
Really? It's just like
everyone else's apartment.
그냥 다른 아파트와 똑같죠
방과 벽, 천장이 있어요
It's got rooms and walls
and ceilings.
사는 모습을 보고 싶어요
구경시켜 주세요
I just wanted to see where you live.
Now give me the tour.
맙소사, 일 났군!
Oh, my God!
- 여긴 거실이고
- 좋네요
-This is the living room.
-That's nice.
-And this is the kitchen.
-That's real pretty.
- 여기는 부엌이구요
- 깔끔하네요
침실 좀 보여주세요
Wait a minute.
Don't I get to see the bedroom?
침실이요?
그냥 전형적인...
Well, it's pretty much your typical...
침실이죠
... bedroom.
We're still on this side of the door.
I didn't get to see it.
너무 순식간이네요
저는 못 봤어요
그럼 다음에 봅시다
Oh, shoot. Maybe next time.
Thanks for a lovely evening.
오늘 고마웠어요
So who is she?
누구예요?
That was the blind date
I told you about.
소개받기로 했던 그 여자야
전화했길래 오늘 만났어
She called
and switched it from Tuesday.
맘에 들어요?
Did you like her?
그냥 친구로서 묻는 거예요
난 정말 괜찮아요
I'm just asking as a friend,
because I am totally fine with this.
Well, you seem fine.
그래 보여
솔직히, 안 괜찮아요
Okay, you know what?
I'm not fine. I'm not.
어떻게 괜찮겠어요?
I mean, how could I be fine?
Hearing you come in with her.
함께 집에 들어오면서
침실을 보자는데...
She wants to see your bedroom.
이건 어때요?
You know what?
친구로 지내면서
애인을 안 만드는 거요
What if we're friends...
...who don't see other people?
You mean "exclusive" friends?
- 서로를 독점하는 친구?
- 싫어요?
Why not?
I mean, this has been
the most amazing week.
저는 이번 주가
너무 즐거웠어요
이러면 안 될까요?
Would it be so terrible?
친구 기분이면서
함께 사는 건요?
Even if we were friends
who lived together?
아니면 여러 친구들 앞에서
친구 언약식이라도 할까요?
Or maybe someday, friends who stood
up in front of their other friends...
...and vowed to be friends forever.
옛날로 돌아온 것 같아
You know, we're back where we were.
나도 그 모든 걸 원해
하지만 변한 게 없잖아
Honey, I would love to do all that,
but nothing's changed.
That's not true.
You don't have a moustache.
아뇨
지금은 콧수염이 없어요
그래, 하나 변했군
Okay, one thing's changed.
But we still want different things,
and we know how this is gonna end.
하지만 우린 목표가 달라서
끝은 똑같을 거야
지금 당장 가는 게
좋겠어요
You know what?
I gotta walk out of here right now.
Because getting over you is the
hardest thing I have ever had to do.
당신을 잊는 게 너무나
고통스러웠거든요
I don't think I could do it again.
두 번 다시
그러고 싶지 않아요
I know I couldn't.
나도 그래
네
그럼...
How about one last
game of racquetball?
라켓볼 한 번 더 칠까요?
Watch the thorns!
장미가시 조심해요
What?
왜?
Beth is really, really sick.
베스가 너무 아파
Jo's there, but I don't think
there's anything she can do.
'조'가 돌보지만
방법이 없나봐
- 조이?
- 응?
You wanna put the book
in the freezer?
그 책도 냉장고에 넣을까?
- 좋아
- 그래